yootheme.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy - YOOtheme

YOOtheme, GmbH (“YOOtheme“, “Company”, “us” or “we”) respects and protects the privacy of visitors to our website, yootheme.com, and our customers who use our web design software and related services (the "Service"). By using the Service in any way, you are agreeing to comply with this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service](https://yootheme.com/terms).

The Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time, without prior notice. You are responsible for reviewing the Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The Privacy Policy applies to all visitors and customers who access the YOOtheme Service.

## 1\. Core Principles

Your privacy really matters to us. At YOOtheme, we are committed to following our core principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our Service, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless it's required for our Service.
  * We don’t sell your personal information.

## 2\. Collection

When you use the Services, we collect the following information and use it only as described below:

### Personal Information

When you purchase our Service, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us including your name, address, contact information, email address, the IP address you used to access the Service and other information. We may also store a cookie on your computer to authenticate your identity.

### Payment Information

When you provide your payment information, it's directly transmitted to our payment processors, heidelpay or PayPal. They use and process your payment information in accordance with their privacy policy. We don’t store your payment information.

### Anonymous Information

When you browse the yootheme.com website, we collect certain statistical, non-personally identifiable information, including your browser type, your referring pages, your use of the Service, the pages you viewed and other similar information.

## 3\. Sharing

When you use the Service, we may share your information only as described below:

### Third Party Services

We may share information about you with third party vendors who need to know information about you in order to provide their services to us. This group includes vendors that help us provide our Service to you, like payment providers that process your credit and debit card information, and those that help us understand and enhance our Service, like analytics providers.

### As Required by Law

We may disclose your information to third parties in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request.

### Business Transfers

In the event YOOtheme goes through a business transition, such as merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your personal information, but not other information, may be transferred as part of that deal.

## 4\. Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately used, lost, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you use credit card as your payment provider, all the information will be encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

## 5\. Children’s Personal Information

YOOtheme does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our Service. If we obtain actual knowledge that any personal information about a child under the age of 13 was collected, that information will be immediately removed without any notice. By using this site, you agree that you are at least 13 years old.

## 6\. Links to Other Websites

When you click on links on this website, they may direct you away from our site. YOOtheme is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
